No, ha, ha. No. I'm going out like this.
(Leonard:)Howard, what did you do?
(Howard:)They're called tattoo sleeves. Look.
Yeah, I bought them online.
Raj got a set too.
(Howard:)Fantastic, right?
Put them on, have sex with some girl
with her business pierced...
(Howard:)...take them off, and I can still be buried
in a Jewish cemetery.
(Sheldon:)You know, I've always wanted
to go to a goth nightclub.
(Howard:)-Really?
-Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)None of you ever see
my practical jokes coming, do you?
(Howard:)Okay, how about you two?
Look, I got some extra tat sleeves.
(Leonard:)Why are you carrying extras?
(Howard:)In case I snag one
on someone's nipple ring.
(Penny:)Yeah, I think we'll pass.
(Howard:)Oh, is the missus speaking
for the couple now?
(Leonard:)In this case, you bet she is.
Ahh. Yes, she's pushy and, yes,
he's whipped, but that's not the expression.